<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Backing Store]]></title>
  <link href="http://dbbnrl.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://dbbnrl.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-01-09T22:39:02-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://dbbnrl.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dan Brown]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bit late to the party]]></title>
    <link href="http://dbbnrl.github.com/blog/2013/01/09/a-bit-late-to-the-party/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-09T22:03:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://dbbnrl.github.com/blog/2013/01/09/a-bit-late-to-the-party</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So, I&#8217;ve finally decided to try out this blogging thing.</p>

<p>Recently I&#8217;ve been fiddling around on a project that (so far) involves simultaneously learning modern OpenGL and Haskell.  And Functional Reactive Programming (FRP).  Oh, and a bit of WXWindows, possibly.</p>

<p>All of which involves getting a lot of concepts straight in my head, which I&#8217;m thinking might be easiest if I take notes, some of which might actually be organized enough for other people to find useful, which suggests that I should look into blogging&#8230;</p>

<p>In my typical premature-optimization, tool-focused style, I created this blog on wordpress.com, discovered through further research that it wasn&#8217;t <em>quite</em> perfect for my needs, and abandoned it the same day (after zero posts) to start getting octopress-over-github configured.  This way is much geekier, which makes it Better.</p>

<p>Oh, and I keep meaning to buy some parts and do a bit of Arduino-based robotics, though at this point I&#8217;ve spent so much time thinking about doing that without actually <em>doing</em> it (including hours of research and a carefully constructed shopping list) that Raspberry Pi may now be a better option.  I should really research that&#8230;</p>

<p>There&#8217;s a pattern here, which I hope to break out of by:</p>

<ul>
<li>Doing things in small increments and committing code to Git frequently, and</li>
<li>Blogging frequently about what I&#8217;m working on.</li>
</ul>


<p>The former has helped my productivity at work quite a bit. (And helped curtail my tendency toward over-design and premature optimization).  The latter is just the application of the same principle to mental output that isn&#8217;t code and doesn&#8217;t go into revision control (though with Github pages, there&#8217;s a certain additional symmetry&#8230;)</p>

<p>I&#8217;m not quite sure why I&#8217;m telling myself these things, it&#8217;s not as if the Internet is listening.  I suppose my audience is really Future Dan.</p>

<p>Hello, Future Dan.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
